[{"answer": "If I was in that job now, I would probably be sitting in Washington waiting for the current crisis to pass.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What would you be doing right now, if you were in that job now?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I think it sounds kind of similar, piers, but I think there is something different this time.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Or is there, as some people, a chance that this could be more serious?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, the amazing thing about north Korea is that it takes totalitarianism to an entirely new level, and besides all the control and the repression, there's a classification system that is superimposed on the entire society.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "What is the significance of that?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "It is an unusual place.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "It is really, as John was saying there, totalitarianism gone crackers, isn't it?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think, right now, I would agree with what Bob said earlier.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "I mean, what should the American administration led by, say, John Kerry in South Korea, how should they be conducting themselves directly with the North Koreans would you say?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Is that true, as far as you're aware?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "It's gotten out of hand.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Why are you doing it and what do you hope to achieve?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "It could be from $50,000 to $100,000 a night, it looks like.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Do you know how much this is all going to cost you, too?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Free coffee, as well.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Free coffee as well?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I mean it's embarrassing.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "-- of America right now?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Oh, they're -- they're out of their frickin' minds.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What do you make of the dysfunction in Washington, where they can't seem to get any kind of budget deals done, any kind of economic plan sorted, nothing?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Do you feel the gap between the rich and poor is just widening all the time now?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "We can come to girls in a moment, don't you worry.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Can't we just talk about fun stuff, girls and lakes, summertime?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I'm pretty confused, though.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "How would you describe where you are politically now?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Just the whole way things were going with -- especially just -- just separating the country even more.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Why did you give up on Obama?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Someone's got to take the blame.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "But was that his fault?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I don't care.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "On the -- on the gay rights, gay marriage thing, are you from the -- you couldn't really give a damn category?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Guns.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "It's very touchy, but I think at the end of the day, man, it's got to fall on the woman, you know?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "The only thing I could think of that might work -- no, I'm not for gun control.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Are you in favor of any gun control?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Yes, tons.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Do you own a lot of guns yourself?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Would you consider yourself to be safe with them?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "It's as simple as that?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I need to have one.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "So you think you need to have one for protection?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "And you wouldn't hesitate to use it?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's families on both sides, from what I've read.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What if you're one of the families from Sandy Hook school?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Yes, and people are -- get so up in arms and get so hell bent one way or the other.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "There's very little compromise, is there?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "That was fun.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "-- and Romney had lost?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "He was -- I've always said this about Obama no matter what, he's cool.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Did he -- did he have a little joke at your expense?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "He probably said, you know, I think when I popped up in the receiving line, I was like -- he's like, Kid Rock, and I'm like, hey, man --", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What -- what did he say to you when he saw you again?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Because it came from Kid, it was expected.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "What goes on in that moment?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I will say we left that night -- I've had many of those dinners.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "A big gamble, though, isn't it?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "That's what Willie Nelson said.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "You got some?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Legalize it, tax the hell out of it.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Good thing?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Simple as that?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Twenty.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "How old is your boy now?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Careful.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "What did you say to him about drugs?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "No, because remember that time I came home, fell down, I think it was Christmas Eve, slept on the bathroom floor.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Not, don't do it?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Kind of, yeah.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "You're a living warning, basically?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I got to have dinner with Clint and just become, you know, I'd say a friend over the last few years.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Is he a mate?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, I'd wrestled with perhaps doing a book one day.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What made you write it?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "That he wouldn't have liked you talking about him?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Well, he had always teased me for all the years that I knew him, all the guys -- I was the youngest.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "How did it come about?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I would imagine to most people it's a fortune.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "But it's a fortune, right?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Wow, that is so, so tough.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "The great moment of your life?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "But it was Bruno who wanted to do more to help families living in area motels.", "docId": "130412pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "After the CNN show, lots of people call me, what can we do for you?", "qSentId": 754}]